<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Exo 02</string>

    <string name="title_info">Information</string>
    <string name="title_call">To Call</string>

    <string name="label_username">Username :</string>
    <string name="lable_phone_number">Phone number :</string>
    <string name="label_password">Password</string>

    <string name="btn_login">Login</string>
    <string name="btn_menu_info">Information</string>
    <string name="btn_menu_call">To Call</string>
    <string name="btn_call">Call</string>

    <string name="img_logo_desc" translatable="false">Della Duck</string>
    <string name="img_main_desc">Picsou house</string>
    <string name="img_cat_desc">Trigun\'s cat</string>

    <string name="cat_lorem">Attack feet behind the couch destroy couch flop over give attitude hide when guests come over hopped up on goofballs hunt anything that moves intrigued by the shower need to chase tail leave dead animals as gifts, all of a sudden go crazy rub face on everything chase mice sweet beast under the bed chase imaginary bugs stand in front of the computer screen chew ipad power cord . Leave dead animals as gifts give attitude stand in front of the computer screen attack feet intently stare at the same spot shake treat chase imaginary bugs flop over all of a sudden go crazy hunt anything that moves rub face on everything, behind the couch destroy couch chase mice need to chase tail hide when guests come over intrigued by the shower sweet beast under the bed chew ipad power cord hopped up on goofballs bag stretch chase imaginary bugs, need to chase tail shake treat hopped up on goofballs intrigued by the shower rub face on everything hide when guests come over sweet beast under the bed destroy couch all of a sudden go crazy.</string>
    <string name="toast_welcome_msg">Welcome %s</string>
    <string name="toast_error_login">Bad credentials !</string>
    <string name="unknown_username">Unknown</string>
    <string name="uri_tel" translatable="false">tel:%s</string>
    <string name="toast_no_call_permission">You need to authorize the application to use your phone, if you want to make a call with it... Without this, it is not possible for the application to make a call (and this is a security feature imposed by Android. Thank you for accepting)!</string>
</resources>